interesting-articles.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy And Terms Of Use

Interesting-articles.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site.  Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Our site uses a registration form for visitors to request information and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address).  Contact information from the registration form is used to send login information to our customers. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

**Spam:** We do not use, nor do we condone the use of unsolicited bulk email. Please report any incidents of unsolicited email coming from or mentioning the interesting-articles.com domain to webmaster(at)interesting-articles.com for a prompt and personal reply. All matters will be investigated and dealt with promptly.

**Your Personal Information:** Our site uses forms for information requests and registrations. Contact information from all forms (including name, address, email address, etc.) is used to process registration requests and mail information about our company to our visitors.

**Children's Guidelines**

We do: NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.

NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent.

NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent.

NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

**Google Ads**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
